<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pismo Coast Real Estate Video Blog with Sylvia Lunsford</title>
    <description>Our mission at Outland and Associates is to be your best resource for Central Coast real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Outland and Associates, your professional Pismo Beach Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:08:24 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:08:24 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Selling Your Home During the Pandemic</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bGwd_84an70?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I speak with clients, I’m continually asked if it’s still possible to sell homes safely during the pandemic, given all the safety measures implemented by the government. Luckily, the answer is yes! Once the buyer has viewed your property online, we’ll then ask them to drive through the neighborhood to see if it all checks out. Before we begin phase two, we’ll make sure the buyer has a pre-approval letter from their lender, and both the buyer’s and seller’s agent will need to sign a new California Association of Realtors form that was specifically created for the pandemic called the Coronavirus Entry Form. To learn what it entails, as well as what comes during phase two of the process, watch this short video above.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 15:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/selling-your-home-during-the-pandemic.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/selling-your-home-during-the-pandemic.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to My Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a real estate professional, I know what’s happening every day in the area, specifically concerning home values and how these trends and developments will directly affect you. Even as this ongoing pandemic is changing our market, I’m out on the front lines to make sure that those changes are communicated to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, I plan to post  two helpful messages each month on this blog to keep you updated and help you stay on top of what’s happening in the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking the time to read this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the way we buy and sell homes is changing, I’m going to be here to help you through it. Let us know if you have any questions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check back because content will be coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m determined to keep you updated on what’s going on with the real estate market. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 09:34:02 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-blog.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
